<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>William Benton</title>
    <description>Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/willb&quot;&gt;@willb on Micro.blog&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    <link>http://mu.willb.io/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 20:13:55 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 20:13:55 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Tracing the development of presentation style</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;For nearly all of my adult life, a large part of my job has involved communicating technical concepts.  I like to imagine that I’ve developed a consistent voice, style, and visual language, and I’m also inclined to imagine that it has taken me a long time to get here.  I recently needed to look over an old deck and was surprised to note that many elements of my current (and presumably at least somewhat refined) style were present in a talk I gave over a decade ago as a graduate student.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s &lt;a href=&quot;http://pages.cs.wisc.edu/~willb/dimple/ppdp07-talk.pdf&quot;&gt;the old talk&lt;/a&gt;; for comparison, here’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://chapeau.freevariable.com/static/201801/probabilistic-structures.pdf&quot;&gt;a talk I gave this January&lt;/a&gt;.  While I’m still improving at giving talks and designing visual explanations, I guess things haven’t changed as radically as I might have assumed.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 20:13:49 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://mu.willb.io/2018/07/23/tracing-the-development.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://willb.micro.blog/2018/07/24/tracing-the-development.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>The delights of cookbooks</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I was reminded today that the delights of good cookbooks subsist not merely in explaining how to prepare particular dishes of interest but in introducing wonderful things &lt;em&gt;that one didn’t even know were of interest&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is true of the best technical writing structured around a cookbook metaphor, as well.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 17:39:29 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://mu.willb.io/2018/07/06/the-delights-of.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://willb.micro.blog/2018/07/06/the-delights-of.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
